<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArrayOfCutscene xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Cutscene>
    <Name>Opening</Name>
    <Actions>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>Everything was good in the world of [Acquesitia].</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>Evil existed in this realm, to be sure, but the hordes of vile monsters were always kept at bay.</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>Adventurers' endless appetites for acquiring new and better [loot] from killing monsters ensured that the forces of evil could never truly rise to power.</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>Then, one day, the [Real Money Auction House] was established.</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>Adventurers could now buy and sell loot using endless supplies of mythical [Real Currency], causing the established gold standard to bottom out.</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>After awhile, adventurers stopped using gold and bartering to trade items altogether, preferring to deal solely with Real Currency.</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>While the adventurers of the world traded items for [Real Currency], the forces of evil, no longer being farmed for their loot, rose to power for the first time in milennia.</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>They began to terrorize the civilizations of Acquesitia, and the adventurers of the world, no longer equipped to fight, found themselves unable to fight back.</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>You are [Stebbins], a grizzled old adventurer who was all set to have an easy retirement as an item vendor (as is often the case for aged heroes), but then all of this happened.</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>Vendors are now obsolete, evil is rising across the land, and you, Stebbins, are homeless, living in an alleyway with what remains of the loot you acquired in your adventuring days.</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
      <CutsceneAction xsi:type="DialogueAction">
        <Text>Despite being [too old for this shit], Stebbins sets out to right the wrongs of the world, the only way he knows: [capitalism].</Text>
      </CutsceneAction>
    </Actions>
  </Cutscene>
</ArrayOfCutscene>